<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ABND_6_TOUR_GUIDE</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="campsite_title">Camp sites</string>
    <string name="trails_title">Trails</string>
    <string name="rest_stops_title">Rest Stops</string>
    <string name="observer_tower_title">Oberserver Towers</string>
    <string name="krapi_campsite">Krapi campsite</string>
    <string name="krapi_campsite_description">The campsite is situated in the shade of old coastal pines on the ca 2 km stretch of the seashore.</string>
    <string name="lake_rae_campsite">Lake Rae campsite</string>
    <string name="lake_rae_campsite_description">The campsite is situated at Lake Rae and is a nice place for a forest recreation, swimming, fishing or hiking on Lake Rae hiking trail. The Kopra tare–Ikla section (74 km) of RMK Hiking Route passes the campsite.</string>
    <string name="lemme_campsite">Lemme campsite</string>
    <string name="lemme_campsite_description">Lemme campsite has been a popular holiday destination among domestic and foreign tourists for dozens of years. The campsite is situated on the seashore in the shade of pine trees and is surrounded by fence. The RMK Hiking Route section Kopra tare–Ikla (74 km) passes the campsite.</string>
    <string name="matsiranna_campsite">Matsiranna campsite</string>
    <string name="matsiranna_campsite_description">The seaside campsite is an attractive place for swimming and camping in the summer months.</string>
    <string name="sootagana_campsite">Soontagana campsite</string>
    <string name="sootagana_campsite_description">The campsite is situated in Avaste Nature Reserve. On the Soontagana bog island you can see the ruins of two farmsteads, the history of which can be traced back 22 generations. The first defence structures of the Soontagana hill fort date from the 7th to 8th century. The campsite boasts a rich historical and cultural legacy—old farm sites, stone walls, cellars.</string>
    <string name="aluoja_observation">Aluoja observation platform</string>
    <string name="aluoja_observation_location">Northern Shore of Lake Peipus Recreation Area</string>
    <string name="harimagi_observation">Harimägi observation tower and campfire site</string>
    <string name="harimagi_observation_location">Otepää Nature Park</string>
    <string name="iisaku_observation">Iisaku observation tower</string>
    <string name="iisaku_observation_location">Northern Shore of Lake Peipus Recreation Area</string>
    <string name="keemu_observation">Keemu observation tower</string>
    <string name="keemu_observation_location">Matsalu National Park</string>
    <string name="ahijarve_rest_stop">Ähijärve rest stop</string>
    <string name="diby_rest_stop">Diby rest stop</string>
    <string name="esku_rest_stop">Esku rest stop</string>
    <string name="harilaiu_rest_stop">Harilaiu rest stop</string>
    <string name="hulkari_rest_stop">Hülkari rest stop</string>
    <string name="ilumetsa_rest_stop">Ilumetsa rest stop (Meteorite Craters)</string>
    <string name="isabella_rest_stop">Isabella rest stop</string>
    <string name="jarve_rest_stop">Järve rest stop</string>
    <string name="jarve_rest_stop_description">"Long beach with golden sands, interesting protected plant species can be found under the pine trees. "</string>
    <string name="ahijarve_rest_stop_description">The recreation site is situated in the yard of the visitor centre of Karula National Park. The recreation site has a table and benches and an outdoor shower with fresh drinking water. A good picnic site. The parking area of the visitor centre is next to the recreation site</string>
    <string name="diby_rest_stop_description" />
    <string name="esku_rest_stop_description">At Esku recreation site you can enjoy the beauty of the forest and listen to the birds sing. In autumn it is a good place to pick mushrooms</string>
    <string name="harilaiu_rest_stop_description">A stopping point for discovering the most north-west peninsula of Saaremaa. At the Harilaiu peninsula you can view rapid natural processes where the sea is in constant battle with the land.</string>
    <string name="hulkari_rest_stop_description">The recreation site offers a magnificent view on Tallinna Bay and Tallinn City. The site is located in the midst of wide and clean sand dunes. The sea by the recreation site is suitable for swimming.</string>
    <string name="ilumetsa_rest_stop_description">Ilumetsa recreation site is situated near meteorite craters in Orava municipality, Põlva County.\nThere is a tourist information cabin, boardwalk, parking area and dry toilet at the recreation site. Camping with tents is not allowed. The site leads to a fascinating walk to the largest meteorite crater here, called Põrguhaud or “Grave of hell”. Wheelchair accessibility."</string>
    <string name="isabella_rest_stop_description" />
    <string name="alatskivi_hiking_trail">Alatskivi hiking trail (4.5 km)</string>
    <string name="allika_hiking_trail">Allika hiking trail (1.2 km)</string>
    <string name="apteekrimagi_hiking_trail">Apteekrimägi hiking trail (4 km)</string>
    <string name="audaku_hiking_trail">Audaku hiking trail (2.8 km)</string>
    <string name="haramae_hiking_trail">Härämäe hiking trail (3.4 km)</string>
    <string name="harilaiu_hiking_trail">Harilaiu hiking trail (11 km or 13 km)</string>
    <string name="huitberg_hiking_trail">Huitberg hiking trail (3 km-2 km)</string>
    <string name="ilmatsalu_karevere_linnutee_hiking_trail">Ilmatsalu–Kärevere Linnutee hiking trail (3,5 km)</string>
    <string name="ilmatsalu_karevere_linnutee_hiking_trail_description">The 3,5 km long “Bird’s Way” hiking trail links the most interesting bird-watching sites in the Tartu area—the Ilmatsalu fish ponds, Kärevere and Alam-Pedja Nature Reserves. The Bird’s Way hiking trail offers visitors exciting experiences throughout the year. The Ilmatsalu fish ponds and the surrounding area are the most popular bird-watching sites among ornithology enthusiasts in the Tartu area. More than 200 species of birds have been spotted on the ponds and in the close surroundings. Several endangered species can be seen in Kärevere Nature Reserve.</string>
    <string name="jalase_hiking_trail">Jalase nature trail (2.6 km)</string>
    <string name="joemoisa_hiking_trail">Jõemõisa hiking trail (0.5 km)</string>
    <string name="kakisilma_vilsandi_hiking_trail">Käkisilma–Vilsandi hiking trail (5 km)</string>
    <string name="kakisilma_vilsandi_hiking_trail_description">Hiking trail goes through the low coastal sea from islet to islet to Vilsandi Island.</string>
    <string name="joemoisa_hiking_trail_description">The 0.5 km forest path offers a fascinating walk for visitors of the recreation area. Those who wish to continue their hike can walk the 3 km Tammeluha hiking trail.</string>
    <string name="jalase_hiking_trail_description" />
    <string name="huitberg_hiking_trail_description">One of the most captivating places on the Vormsi Island is the Huitberg limestone outcrop in the middle of a spruce forest, in the centre of the island. This more than 400 million years old coral reef smoothed by glacial abrasion has formed from calcareous exoskeletons of animals living in the shallow tropical seas during the Ordovician. On the outcrop, where it is not covered with moss, you can admire fossils or rare protected ferns growing in limestone cavities.</string>
    <string name="harilaiu_hiking_trail_description">Diverse and deserted coastal nature. Low and vast horizon, wind, golden sand and mighty waves. Interesting dune landscape, trees and bushes subjected to wind, seal and bird sounds, military objects and Kiipsaare lighthouse in the sea.</string>
    <string name="haramae_hiking_trail_description">The hiking trail is 3.4 km long, starts on the Hallimägi hill and passes through varied landscape as typical to the Haanja area. The trail descends to the valley, where beavers have created their kingdom. Before the trail gets to the Härämägi hill it is possible to explore different forest types. On Härämägi a view opens on the water-bodies that form the spawning area for the northern crested newt. Other attractions include the Sapas’ arboretum, Härämäe village landscape and architecture. The trail is equipped with wooden signs and information boards.</string>
    <string name="audaku_hiking_trail_description">"Viidumäe Nature Reserve is located in the western part of Saaremaa, in the vicinity of the ancient Antsülusjärve escarpment. This is the oldest and highest part of the Saaremaa island, with its top height 59 metres over the sea level. On the escarpment a number of biotopes characteristic of western Saaremaa can be found. The hiking trail starts and ends at the parking area near the office of Viidumäe Nature Reserve. "</string>
    <string name="apteekrimagi_hiking_trail_description">Apteekrimägi forest trail is a 4 km loop trail with varied terrain and is excellent for jogging or walking. The trail starts and ends in Mäe street, Otepää, in front of Otepää Sports School. There are 4 large boards with the map of the trail and 2 training sites with logs for log lifting.</string>
    <string name="allika_hiking_trail_description">Lake Prästviigi in the centre of the Vormsi Island is a former lagoon overgrown in reeds. The lake’s bird population is abundant and diverse, and on silent spring nights you might hear the calling of Eurasian bittern. In the northern part of the lake are numerous springs, the largest of which is Suurallikas (“great spring”) or Ohvriallikas (“sacrificial spring”). The hiking trail leads to the observation tower on the northern shore of Lake Prästviigi.</string>
    <string name="alatskivi_hiking_trail_description">The 4.5 km hiking trail runs around Lake Lossijärv next to the famous Alatskivi Manor, and with its alternating terrain, various sights and diverse biota offers wonderful experiences in all seasons.</string>
</resources>
